{
    "id": "cbf297de39df46a58708511b484637a4",
    "title": "So or Such Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "90941979ac0c4c91bc786d9cf5989543",
            "title": "So And Such Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "It was ....................... a hot day.",
                    "description": "We use 'such' before adjective + noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You are ....................... kind.",
                    "description": "We use 'so' before an adjective. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "such"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have ...................... a lot of problems that I am losing hope.",
                    "description": "Such is used before adjective + noun. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "such",
                        "so much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Never have I seen ........................ beautiful woman.",
                    "description": "We use 'such a/an' before adjective + singular countable noun. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "so a",
                        "so",
                        "such",
                        "such a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have never seen ........................... food.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "so much",
                        "so many",
                        "such much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Never have I seen .............................. dirty kitchen.",
                    "description": "We use 'such a/an' before adjective + singular countable noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a",
                        "so",
                        "so a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have never seen ........................... a good person.",
                    "description": "Such is used before (adjective) + noun. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "so",
                        "so much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They are ........................... idiots.",
                    "description": "We use such before a noun with or without an adjective. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such an",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has got ...................... strange manners.",
                    "description": "Such is used before a noun with or without an adjective. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "such",
                        "such a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is ..................... patient with his students.",
                    "description": "We use 'so' before adjectives and adverbs. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Why do you talk ........................ loudly?",
                    "description": "We can use so before adverbs.",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We have got ............................. much to do, and ................. little time.",
                    "description": "We can use 'so' before much, many, few and little. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "so, so",
                        "so, such",
                        "such, so",
                        "such, such"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}